这是菏泽市二零二四年初中学业水平考试英语试题听力部分。听力部分共分四个小节，做题时先将答案标在试卷上。录音内容结束后，请将试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。第一节，听下面五个句子，每个句子后有三幅图画。每个句子仅读一遍，请你从每。你所给的
,B 1. The pencil on the desk is mine.
三个选项中，选出与句子内容相符的图画，并标在试卷的相应位置。
2. Lucy often goes to school at 7.30 in the morning.
3. Jerry was sleeping when the rainstorm came.
4. We are not allowed to take photos in the history museum.
5. Chinese people often put paper cuttings on windows to celebrate the spring
festival.,B 6.
第二节，听下面五个句子，每个句子后有一道小题。每个句子读两遍，请你听完句子的第二遍朗读后，从每。每题所给的三个选项中选出最佳答语，并标在试卷的相应位置
What animals do you like?
7. How is the weather today?
8. How often do you exercise,
Lei? 9. You'd better talk to your parents about the problem.
10. What small things can we do to save the
第三节，听下面五段。对话。每段对话后有一道小题，每段对话和问题读两遍。请你听完对话和问题的第二遍朗读后，从每题所给的
,B 11. When is your birthday, Linda?
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标。都在试卷的相应位置。
My birthday is on May 1st.
What about yours, John?
It's on June 15th.
When is your birthday, Linda?
My birthday is on May 1st.
What about yours, John?
It's on June 15th.
Question. When is John's birthday?
When is John's birthday?
12. Hello, this is Jenny.
Hi, Jenny. This is David.
What are you doing now?
I'm doing my homework.
Would you like to play tennis with me?
I'd love to, but I have to finish my homework first.
Hello, this is Hi, Jenny.
This is David.
What are you doing now?
I'm doing my homework.
Would you like to play tennis with me?
I'd love to, but I have to finish my homework first.
Question. What's Jenny doing now?
What's Jenny doing now?
13. Wasn't that a talent show?
Yeah. Who did you think was the best act?
Well, in my opinion, Eliza was the best.
She's an excellent piano player.
she's great. And I thought Steve was the
Me too. I couldn't stop laughing.
I'd say Vera was the most amazing singer.
Wasn't that a talent show?
Yeah. Who did you think was the best act?
in my opinion, Eliza was the best.
She's an excellent piano player.
Yeah, she's great.
And I thought Steve was the funniest.
Me too. I couldn't stop laughing.
I'd say Vera was the most amazing singer.
Question. Who was the in the talent show?
was the funniest in the talent show?
14. Tom, what's the matter with you?
I have a terrible toothache.
You should see a dentist and get an x -ray.
But will it hurt?
No. And if you don't go to the dentist now, it'll hurt even more later.
Tom, what's the matter with you?
I have a terrible toothache.
You should see a dentist and get an x -ray.
But will it hurt?
No. And if you don't go to the dentist now, it'll hurt even more later.
Question. Where will the boy probably go next?
15. Good evening.
May I take your order?
Yes. I'd like some noodles, please.
What kind of noodles would you like?
I'd like beef noodles with carrots.
Sure. What size would you like?
Large, please. Good evening.
May I take your order?
Yes. I'd like some noodles, please.
What kind of noodles would you like?
I'd like beef noodles with carrots.
Sure. What size would you like?
Large, please. Question.
What's the probable relationship between the speakers?
Question. the speakers?
第四节，听下面一段短文。短文后有五道小题。短文和问题读两遍，请你听完短文和问题的第二遍朗读后，从每。以所给的三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
What's the between the
Hi, I'm Jack, and I come from New York.
I came to China for work three years ago.
I work as an English teacher in a middle school in Shanghai now.
When I am free, I like to visit interesting places in China.
Last weekend, I had a great time in Hainan.
I flew to Sanya on Saturday morning.
I booked a hotel with a swimming pool.
The hotel was near the sea, and I could see the beach from my room.
In the evening, I went to a night market and tasted some delicious seafood.
The next day, I went to the beach.
It was clean, and the water was really warm.
I spent one hour swimming in the sea and two hours relaxing on the beach.
I had lunch in a small restaurant nearby.
After lunch, I met some really nice people, and we played beach volleyball together.
In the evening, I flew back to Shanghai.
It was an excellent weekend for me.
I'm going to visit more places of interest in China.
Hi, I'm Jack, and I come from New York.
I came to China for work three years ago.
I work as an English teacher in a middle school in Shanghai now.
When I am free, I like to visit interesting places in China.
Last weekend, I had a great time in Hainan.
I flew to Sanya on Saturday morning.
I booked a hotel with a swimming pool.
The hotel was near the sea, and I could see the beach from my room.
In the evening, I went to a night market and tasted some delicious seafood.
The next day, I went to the beach.
It was clean, and the water was really warm.
I spent one hour swimming in the sea, and two hours relaxing on the beach.
I had lunch in a small restaurant nearby.
After lunch, I met some really nice people, and we played beach volleyball together.
In the evening, I flew back to Shanghai.
It was an excellent weekend for me.
I'm going to visit more places of interest in China.
16. When did Jack come to China?
When did Jack come to China?
17. How did Jack go to Sanya?
did Jack go to Sanya?
18. Where did Jack go on Saturday evening?
Where did Jack go on Saturday evening?
on evening? 19.
How long did Jack swim in the sea?
long did Jack swim in the sea?
20. What did Jack think of his weekend?
What did Jack think of his weekend?
听力考试到此结束，请做其他。他题目，祝同学们取得好成绩